https://musselbeachcampground.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyWho We AreOur website address is: https://musselbeachcampground.com.  We operate Mussel Beach Campground, near Ucluelet in British Columbia.What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect ItContact formsWe do not save any personal data entered into our Reservation Enquiry form.  This data is submitted one time only via email solely for the purposes of reserving a campsite at Mussel Beach Campground..Embedded content from other websitesPages on this site may include embedded content (e.g. YouTube videos). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsNo analytics are enable for this website.Who We Share Your Data WithYour data is used solely by Mussel Beach Campground to administer booking reservations and enquiries.  It is not sold or shared with anyone else.What Rights You Have Over Your DataIf you submit a Reservation Enquiry through the form on this website, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Your Contact InformationThis information is collected and used solely for the purposes of administering your campground reservation, or to answer any questions that you submit by email to musselbeachcamp@gmail.com.
